## SAMUEL JUMA OMODING

P.O Box 1021 GPO Nairobi

+254707195202

jumaomoding@gmail.com

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Dedicated and experienced Customer Care Representative with a background in providing exceptional customer support. Proficient in various customer service tools and techniques. Skilled Meteorologist with a strong analytical background. Committed to delivering accurate and reliable weather forecasts.

#### EDUCATION

#### Kamata School of Music, Nairobi, Kenya

Certificate in Video and Photography.

### University of Nairobi, Nairobi, Kenya

Bachelor of Science in Meteorology

#### Sigalame Boys High School, Busia, Kenya

Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### April 2023 - To date

Customer Service • Customer Care Representative • Optica Limited

#### May 2021 - To date

Customer Care Representative • Part Time • Solar Panda Kenya Limited

#### Feb 2022 - Jan 2023

Meteorologist • Intern • Kenya Meteorological Department

#### KEY SKILLS -

# Data Analysis Numerical Simulation Software Proficiency (Zoho, Webwab, Digium Switchvox, GFFS, ArcGis, WIMES, SURFER 8, MYSTAT)

**Customer Relations** 

#### REFERENCES

Dr. Johnson I. Kinyua, Dean of Students, University of Nairobi P.O Box 30197-00100, GPO, Nairobi jkinyua@uonbi.ac.ke

Mr. Antony Makau, Customer Care Manager, Solar Panda Kenya Limited

746 Muchai Drive

P.O Box 19400-00100GPO, Nairobi antonym@solarpanda.com

Mr. Mwai Zacharia, Assistant Director/ GIS Expert, Kenya Meteorological Department

P.O Box 30259-00100, GPO, Nairobi mwazack@gmail.com